(Bernadette:)Throw the damn ball!
(Amy:)So when do you guys
plan on getting married?
(Penny:)Uh, we're not sure.
But I want to wait long enough
(Penny:)to prove to my mother
I'm not pregnant.
(Sheldon:)May I have
one of your fries?
(Amy:)Of course.
(Amy:)Can I have a bite
of your burger?
(Sheldon:)Absolutely not.
(Leonard:)Some perfect couple.
(Leonard:)He won't even share
his food with her.
(Sheldon:)It has avocado on it.
(Sheldon:)She's allergic
to avocado.
(Sheldon:)Are you so jealous
of our relationship
(Sheldon:)you want Amy to die?
(Leonard:)I'm not jealous.
(Leonard:)I just think it's silly for
you to compare relationships
(Leonard:)like they're something
that can be quantified.